companylist.org 2014-09-17

# Privacy Policy

CompanyList.org is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy, which is a binding part of CompanyList.org's Website Terms of Use and End User License Agreement, explains the type of information CompanyList.org collects through its website and what CompanyList.org does with it. 

What types of information does CompanyList.org collect? 

We collect the following information:   
Focuse on searching and analyzing detailed enterprises information;   
Provide suppliers with the opportunity for them insight into the up-to-date international trade situation, especially the suppliers, own status.   
For buyers, helps finding high quality suppliers efficiently. 

What does CompanyList.org do with the information it collects? 

General speaking,We use your Collected Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our   
content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service specifically for you.We may use your Collected Information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our Users. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users. We may use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your Collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message. 

Registration Information: We may use your Registration Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which CompanyList.org determines that you might be interested. Specifically, we may use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the RegistrationInformation for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. 

Publishing Information: All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. Any Publishing Information that you disclose to CompanyList.org becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information that you submit to us. 

Disclosure of Information: We reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of CompanyList.org, our Users, customers,partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.   
We also reserve the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.   
If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of the Terms of User Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such User's Collected Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to ours. 

How is your information protected? 

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.As a Registered User, your Registration Information and Publishing Information can be viewed and edited through your Account which   
is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser   
window when you have finished your session.No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

Changes to Privacy Policy   
Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact CompanyList.org in writing (at the address set out in the Notice provision of the Terms of Use Agreement) and specifically request that CompanyList.org return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information in CompanyList.org's possession.
